http://www.sssb.com/privacy/

Skip to main contentAdjust Contrast( Press C )Text Size( Press T )Sitemap( Press S )Accessibility Statement( Press A )Close Toolbar( Press Escape )AccessibilityOptionsOnline Banking LoginsConsumer Online BankingLoginNew Consumer Online Banking Users: Enroll NowOnline Banking FAQs |
Mobile Banking FAQsBusiness Online BankingLoginTo enroll in Business Online Banking, visit your local branch.Check My BrowserAdditional Logins:eStatements non Home BankingUChoose Rewards PointsPersonalBusinessWealth ManagementResourcesOnline ServicesSearch SiteSearchcloseHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyRev February 2018FACTSWHAT DOES SOUTH SHORE BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and payment historyCredit history and credit scoresWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information, the reasons South Shore Bank chooses to share, and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes South Shore Bank share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes -such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes -to offer our products and services to youYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes –information about your transactions and experiencesNoWe don't shareFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes –information about your creditworthinessNoWe don't shareFor our affiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareQuestions?Call (781) 682-3715 or go to www.southshorebank.com.Who we areWho is providing the notice?South Shore Bank, 1530 Main Street, Weymouth, MA 02190  (781) 682-3715What we doHow does South Shore Bank protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal & state law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard personal information. We restrict access to your personal and account information to employees who have a business reason.How does South Shore Bank collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youopen an account or deposit moneypay your bills or apply for a loanuse your credit debit cardWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.Why can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates for everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  See below for more on your rights under state law.DefinitionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.South Shore Bank has no affiliatesNon-affiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.South Shore Bank does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.Joint MarketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products and services to you.Our joint marketing partner(s) include the credit card company, which provides our jointly branded card.Other Important InformationSpecial Notice for State ResidentsVermont Residents: We will automatically limit the disclosure of your confidential information within and outside of South Shore Bank in accordance with Vermont law.Personal BankingBusiness BankingWealth Management ServicesResourcesOnline ServicesHours & LocationsAboutHours & LocationsApply For a LoanPrivacy PolicyOnline Privacy PracticesRatesNewsletter Sign UpContact UsView Current RatesNewsletter Sign Up
